iwebchk.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy | Comprehensive Website Review and Analysis

### Privacy Policy

At iwebchk, we understand the trust you place in us while providing your private information, and in return the responsibility we have to protect your privacy. Therefore, we would like to share what information we collect when you use our comprehensive website review and analysis tool, why we collect the information and how we will use it to improve your experience while using iwebchk. By using the iwebchk comprehensive website review & analysis tool, you consent to the data practices that will be expressed in this privacy policy. The purpose of our Privacy Policy is to outline our practices in this area.

**What information do we gather?**

iwebchk.com gathers and uses any website information to run the comprehensive website review and analysis tool as well as to be able to provide the services you have requested. Information like this could include: domain names, server information, IP addresses, estimated traffic, websites content, SEO analysis, usability, access times, HTTP request information and links. Any of this information is used by iwebchk.com to run the service and to create general statistics regarding the iwebchk.com comprehensive website review & analysis tool.

Our web server collects general information with the help of cookies. Cookies are small files that the site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

iwebchk.com tool gathers and collects all data for the modules from public sources online. Therefore, they can be accessed manually online by others since the information is publicly available online (Whois, Alexa, Google, Dmoz, W3C). This is why each report generated on www.iwebchk.com is considered "public", and is stored in our database. Additionally every single report can be indexed by search engines which may place them in searches online.

**Use of Personal Information**

Iwebchk.com may use your personally identifiable email address to inform you of other products or services available from Iwebchk.com and its affiliates. Iwebchk.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.

Iwebchk.com does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. Iwebchk.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (name, address, e-mail, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. 

This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Security of your Personal Information**

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. At this time iwebchk.com uses a third-party payment gateway. PayPal is a leading global online payment company. Follow the link to read [PayPal's privacy policy](https://cms.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US) regarding the payment processing and security. 

Your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on iwebchk.com servers.

**Changes to this Statement**

Iwebchk.com reserves right to update this Statement of Privacy at any time to reflect company and customer feedback. Iwebchk.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Iwebchk.com is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Modified" date below.

This policy was last modified on 01/01/2012
